Senior Technical Lead III

ROBERT SMITH

Phone: (123) 456 78 99
Email: info@qwikresume.com
Website: www.qwikresume.com
LinkedIn: linkedin.com/qwikresume
Address: 1737 Marshville Road,

Alabama

Objective

Having 11+ years of IT industry experience encompassing a wide range of skill set and industry verticals. Worked in onsite as onsite coordinator and lead for 4+ years and Extensive experience with analysis, design, development, customization and implementation of software applications in SAP Technology.

Skills

SAP ABAP, ALE Idocs, ABAP Reports, ABAP Data Dictionary, SAP Upgrade.

Work Experience

Senior Technical Lead III

Mars Project - October 2009 - 2020

- Responsible for leading a team and coordinating in delivering solutions to Mars Information Services.
- Delivered new and complex high quality solutions to clients in response to varying business requirements.
- Worked as abap release management lead and coordinator for the releases in the Mars.
- Worked on the Atlas system during upgrade of systems using SPDD and SPAU transactions.
- Interacted and updated the status development during weekly review meetings.
- Involved in Job Scheduling, monitoring and reporting techniques.
- Assigned the Work to Team members and to monitor the progress of the development.

Senior Technical Lead

Delta Corporation - 2004 - 2009

- from Jun 15 to present understanding of heat transfer Design and simulation of Electronic device in Thermal/CFD/FEA areas.
- · systems, and fluid dynamics.
- ACCOUNTABILITIES Actively involved in the development support of Feature Enhancement using Java, J2EE & SNMP in Insight Element Management System.
- Maintained and extended existing software, designed and wrote code for new functionality Skills Used C#.NET, MS Excel, MS Outlook, Visual Studio 2012,.
- Worked for HCL Technologies Ltd, as a Technical Lead from July 2010 March 2014.
- Worked for Wipro Technologies Ltd, Bangalore as a Senior Software Engineer From Jan 2006 -Oct 2009 Worked for Safran Aerospace India, Bangalore as a .
- · Firmware modifications for the Surface family of tablets.

Education

Bachelor of Technology - (Sri Venkateshwara University - Tirupati, Andhra Pradesh)